他们如何对待你？
How do they treat you?
¿Cómo te tratan a ti?
很好，从一开始大家就对我很好。
Very good, from the first moment everyone has treated me very well.
Muy bien, desde el primer momento todos me han tratado muy bien.
工作人员、教练组、队友，非常高兴。
the staff, the coaching staff, the teammates, so very happy.
el staff, el cuerpo técnico, los compañeros, así que muy contento.
太阳。
The sun.
El sol.
阳光也很好。
The sun too, very good.
El sol también, muy bien.
它有助于到达一个地方，与几个男孩一起，
It helps to get to a place where, with several of the boys,
ayuda el llegar a un sitio donde, con varios de los chicos,
你们有一段共同的历史，就像世界杯一样给你们留下了深刻的印记。
You have a history in common that marked you as much as the World Cup.
Tienes una historia en común que te marcó tanto, además, como el Mundial.
是的，显然，因为你认识的人。
Yes, obviously, because people you know.
Sí, obviamente, porque gente que uno conoce.
朋友们，正如我在分享了这么多时刻后所说的
friends and as I said after having shared so many moments
amigos y como decía al haber compartido tantos momentos
例如在选择和更多...
for example in the selection and more...
por ejemplo en la selección y más...
获得头衔，会让工会更加强大。
Getting titles, that makes the union even stronger.
Obteniendo títulos, eso hace que la unión sea aún más fuerte.
去一个你认识的人的地方会让一切变得容易得多。
Getting to a place where you know people makes everything much easier.
llegar a un lugar donde conoces gente se hace todo mucho más fácil.
他们带你出去见你了吗？
Have they taken you out to meet you?
¿Te han sacado a conocer?
还不是很多，已经有很多比赛了，但是一点一点是的。
Not much yet, there have been many games, but little by little yes.
Todavía no mucho, han sido muchos partidos, pero de a poquito sí.
你们进行了哪些谈话最终告诉您，我们去加莱蒂吧？
What conversation did you have that ended up telling you, let's go to Galetti?
¿Qué charla tuviste que te terminó de decir, vamos a Galetti?
有很多事情
There were many things
Fueron muchas cosas
一个必须一点一点做出的决定。
a decision that had to be made little by little.
una decisión que tenía que tomar de a poco.
我是一个人处理的，然后我显然咨询了那些人
I was processing it alone, then I obviously consulted with those who
lo fui procesando solo, después consulta obviamente con los que
一个人更亲近，包括家人、女朋友、朋友，然后与一些男孩交谈。
One is closer, family, girlfriend, friends and then talks with some of the boys.
Uno tiene más cerca, familia, novia, amigos y después charlas con algunos de los chicos.
我们之前讨论过，我已经知道了。
that we were talking about before, that I already know.
que hablábamos antes, que ya conozco.
他们告诉你什么？
And what did they tell you?
¿Y qué te decían?
俱乐部里的人如何形容你？
How did they describe you in the club?
¿Cómo te describían en el club?
我太酷了，我会很舒服，他们会让我感觉很好。
I was so cool, I was going to be very comfortable, they were going to make me feel very good.
Que iñera, que iba a estar muy cómodo, que me iban a hacer sentir muy bien.
俱乐部非常好，我必须从一开始就体验它。
that the club was very nice, that I had to experience it from the beginning.
que el club era muy lindo, que tenía que vivirlo desde el principio.
进去就知道马德里竞技意味着什么。
inside to know what Athletic de Madrid means.
adentro para saber lo que significa el Athletic de Madrid.
乔洛也是。
Cholo too.
El Cholo también.
我也和安托万谈了很多，他告诉我
I also talked a lot with Antoine who told me that
Hablaba mucho también con Antoine que me decía que
而且粉丝们都很漂亮，我快要坠入爱河了，所以好吧，所有这些事情都有点……
Also that the fans were very pretty, that I was going to fall in love, so well, all those things were a bit...
que también que la hinchada era muy linda, que me iba a enamorar, así que bueno, un poco todas esas cosas fueron...
阿根廷孩子们告诉你，阿根廷是什么样的球迷？
And the Argentine kids tell you, what fan does Argentina look like?
Y los chicos argentinos te dicen, ¿a qué hincha se parece Argentina?
不，我不知道是否……或者存在争论。
No, I don't know if... Or there is debate.
No, no sé si... O hay debate.
我不知道罗德里格斯是否参加比赛，对吧？
I don't know if... Rodríguez has the race, right?
No sé si... Rodríguez tiene la raza, ¿no?
是的，当然，好吧，到你身边去。
Yes, of course, well, go to your side.
Sí, claro, bueno, tira para su lado.
但不，每个人都说在西班牙这里是......
but no, everyone says that here in Spain it is...
pero no, todos dicen que acá en España es...
的改进，那么好吧，我们看到了什么
of the improvements, so well, we saw what
de las mejoras, así que bueno, se vio lo
老实说，我在这些比赛中生活得很好，在体育场里生活得很好。
I lived in these games and very well, honestly, in the Stadium.
viví en estos partidos y muy bien, la verdad, en el Estadio.
他给你发了很多WhatsApp，想想看。
He sent you a lot of WhatsApp, think about it.
Te mandó mucho WhatsApp, pensélo.
是的，有一点。
Yes a bit.
Sí, un poco.
一些电话、WhatsApp，什么都做一点。
Some calls, WhatsApp, a little bit of everything.
Algunas llamadas, WhatsApp, un poco de todo.
你已经开始了解他了。
You already started to know him.
ya lo empezaste a conocer.
是在乐队中更强烈，还是在 WhatsApp 和通话中更强烈？
Is it more intense in the band or with WhatsApp and calls?
¿Es más intenso en la banda o con los WhatsApp y las llamadas?
嗯，一开始它有点带有消息，它还发送了......
And well, at the beginning it was a bit with a message, it also sent...
Y bueno, ahí al principio estuvo un poco con mensaje, también mandaba...
一些写信给我的人。
some who wrote to me.
algunos que me escribieran.
朱利亚诺也是。
Juliano too.
Juliano también.
你听说过这个，对吧？
You heard about that, right?
Te enteraste de eso, ¿no?
与朱利安一起分享奥运会。
together sharing the Olympic Games with Julián.
junto compartiendo los Juegos Olímpicos con Julián.
没有什么，你也可以在比赛和训练中看到它，也非常激烈，非常夸张。
And nothing, you also see it in games, in training, also very intense, very over the top.
Y nada, también se ve en los partidos, en los entrenamientos, también muy intenso, muy encima.
你喜欢这样吗？
Do you like that?
¿Te gusta eso?
是的，这很好，因为它需要你。
Yes, it's good because it demands you.
Sí, está bueno porque te exige.
尝试成长，找到你最好的版本，所以这很好，因为......
Try to grow, to find your best version, so that's good because...
Intenta buscar que crezca, que encuentres tu mejor versión, entonces eso es bueno porque...
因为这就是一个人想要的，成长，学习很多东西，我对此总是持开放态度。
because that is what one wants, to grow, to learn many things and I am always open to that.
porque es lo que uno quiere, crecer, aprender muchas cosas y yo siempre estoy abierto a eso.
你带我去那个演讲。
You take me to that talk.
Me llevas a esa charla.
总有一个人告诉你……她说服了我。
There is always one that tells you... She convinced me.
Siempre hay una que te dice... Me convenció.
他告诉我一些我说过的话，我想走那条路，我想走那条路。
He told me something that I said, I want to go that way, I want to follow that path.
me dijo algo que dije, quiero ir por ahí, quiero seguir ese camino.
嗯，我想这是我第一个得到的，它向我解释了如何......
Well, I think it was one of the first ones I had that explained to me a little how...
Bueno, creo que fue una de las primeras que tuve que me explicó un poco cómo...
俱乐部如何运作，他对我的要求，他对我的期望。
how the club worked, what he wanted from me, what he expected from me.
cómo funcionaba el club, lo que quería de mí, lo que esperaba de mí.
俱乐部今年和未来的项目。
the project that is coming up in the club for this year and those to come.
el proyecto que se viene en el club para este año y los que vienen.
是什么让你点击了？
And what made you click?
¿Y qué es lo que te hizo clic?
你喜欢他告诉你的什么？
What did you like about what he told you?
¿Qué es lo que te gustó de eso que te dijo?
嗯，他对待足球的方式，对足球的热情......
Well, the way he lives football, the passion with which...
Bueno, la forma en la que él vive el fútbol, la pasión con la que...
你看到了它，它传达了什么，不仅是Cholo，还有场上的整个团队。
that you see it, that what it transmits, well not only Cholo but the entire team on the field.
que se lo ve, que lo que transmite, bueno no solo el Cholo sino todo el equipo en la cancha.
这是引起我注意的事情，也是因为我认为它是......
It was something that caught my attention and also because I thought it was...
Era algo que me llamaba la atención y también porque pensaba que era...
这是一个我可以找到我最好的版本的地方，所以也是这样。
which is a place where I can find my best version, so it was also that way.
que es un lugar en el que puedo encontrar mi mejor versión, entonces también fue por ese lado.
听着，让我们来看第一个对象，因为它与激情有关。
Look, let's go to the first object, because it has to do with passion.
Mira, vamos al primer objeto, porque tiene que ver con la pasión.
这是莱蒂围巾。
This is a Lety scarf.
Esta es una bufanda de la Lety.
它说什么？
What does it say?
¿Qué dice?
勇气和心。
Courage and heart.
Coraje y corazón.
勇气和心。
Courage and heart.
Coraje y corazón.
就是这样，不是吗？
That's it, isn't it?
Es eso, ¿no?
我的意思是，你感觉...
I mean, you feel like...
Digo, te sentís como...
就像在阿根廷的俱乐部一样。
like in a club in Argentina.
como en un club de Argentina.
它有那个...
It has that...
Tiene ese...
是联播吗？
Is it hookup?
¿Es enganche?
是的，就是这样。
Yes, it's something like that.
Sí, es algo así.
这些话已经说明了一切，我们刚才谈论的是激情等等。
The words say it, what we were just talking about about passion and all that.
Las palabras lo dicen, lo que hablábamos recién de pasión y todo eso.
团队合作以及良好的怎么说
teamwork and good how to also say something
trabajo de equipo y bueno como decir también algo
对于阿根廷人来说，我们对足球的感受，我们的生活方式，也都是这些。
of Argentine, what we also feel about football, how we live, it's a bit of all that too.
de argentino, lo que sentimos también por el fútbol, cómo se vive, es un poco todo eso también.
罗德里，很健谈，很擅长告诉你事情，很善于交朋友。
Rodri, who is very talkative and very good at telling you things, very good at mates.
Rodri, que es muy de hablar y muy de contarte cosas, de matear.
一些你喜欢的谈话，他告诉你什么，等待着你的是什么，游戏是如何体验的。
some talk that you liked, what he told you, what awaited you, how the games are experienced.
alguna charla que te haya gustado, lo que te dijo, de lo que te esperaba, de cómo se viven los partidos.
不，好吧，当他在那里给我发消息时，这并不是一个话题。
No, well, when he sent me messages there it wasn't so much of a topic.
No, bueno, cuando me mandaba mensaje por ahí no era tanto de tema.
专业人士，可以这么说，如果没有，那就来吧，玩得开心。
professionals, so to speak, if not, come on, have a good time.
profesionales, por así decirlo, si no, dale, venite, pasa bien.
所有这些东西都会对我们有很大帮助。
and all that kind of stuff is going to help us a lot and all that.
y todo ese tipo de cosas nos va a ayudar mucho y todo eso.
我不知道这是否是特定的，但是是的，在日常生活中，他非常亲密，他非常活跃，他喜欢......
I don't know if it's something specific, but yes, on a day-to-day basis he is very close, he is very active, he likes to be...
No sé si algo puntual, pero sí, en el día a día está muy cerca, él es muy activo, le gusta estar...
整天都是情意绵绵。
All day the affection.
Todo el día el afecto.
它通过联系来移动，所以这很好，伙伴和所有这些谈话。
It moves by connections, so that's good, the mate and all those talks.
Se mueve por las conexiones, entonces eso bueno, el mate y todas esas charlas.
它们使日常适应变得更好。
They make day-to-day adaptation much better.
hacen que la adaptación del día a día sea mucho mejor.
这就是罗德里的角色，对吧？
That's a bit of Rodri's role, right?
Ese es un poco el rol de Rodri, ¿no?
他在国家队也有这样的表现，在这里也是如此。
He had that in the national team, here too.
En la selección tuvo eso, acá también.
团结团队，对吗？
unites the group, right?
une el grupo, ¿no?
属...
Genera...
活动、谈话，让大家都朝着同一个方向拉，感觉舒服。
activities, talks, so that everyone is pulling in the same direction, feels comfortable.
actividades, charlas, para que todo el mundo esté pateando para el mismo lado, se sienta cómodo.
气氛很好。
there is a good atmosphere.
haya buen ambiente.
显然，每个人都有自己的角色和生活方式，但是，罗德里确实有一点。
And each one obviously has their role, their way of being, but yes, Rodri really has a little of that.
Y cada uno obviamente tiene su rol, su forma de ser, pero sí, de verdad que Rodri tiene un poco de eso.
试图团结这个群体，不同的......
of trying to unite the group, the different...
de tratar de unir el grupo, los distintos...
与任何团队一样，到处都有一定的亲和力群体。
As in any team, everywhere there is a certain affinity group.
Como en todo equipo, en todos lados hay cierto grupo por afinidad.
也有一点是因为他的生活方式。
Also a little of that because of his way of being.
También un poco de eso por la forma de ser de él.
他非常活跃。
He is very active.
Él es muy activo.
他非常喜欢调皮，他想一直做爱，这很有帮助。
He likes it very mischievous, he wants to fuck all the time and that helps.
Le gusta muy pícaro, quiere todo el tiempo joder y eso ayuda.
当一切变得专业和非常严肃时，一切都会变得不满意。
that everything out there when it is professional and everything very serious becomes dissatisfied.
que todo por ahí cuando es profesional y todo muy serio se descontenta.
稍微契约一下，多一些这种友谊，每天分享。
contract a little and have more of this friendship, of sharing on a daily basis.
contractuar un poco y tenga más de esto de amistad, de compartir en el día a día.
嘿……我要把围巾拿出来。
Hey... I'm going to take out the scarf.
Eh... Voy a sacar la bufanda.
我想问你变革什么时候开始成熟。
I wanted to ask you when the change begins to mature.
Quería preguntarte cuándo comenzas a madurar el cambio.
你什么时候说我的职业生涯必须在城外继续下去？
What is the moment when you say my career has to continue outside the city?
¿Cuál es el momento que decís mi carrera tiene que seguir fuera del city?
不，好吧，一开始不是。
No, well, not at first.
No, bueno, al principio no.
我没有那样想。
I didn't think about it that way.
No lo pensaba así.
我参加了美洲杯，然后是奥运会。
I had the Copa América, then the Olympic Game.
Tuve Copa América, después Juego Olímpico.
不过好在，一会儿……
But well, in a moment...
Pero bueno, en un momento...
独自思考，我觉得我需要......
Thinking alone, I felt like I needed...
Pensando solo, sentía que necesitaba...
我的足球生涯发生了变化，一个新的挑战。
a change in my football career, a new challenge.
un cambio en mi carrera futbolística, un nuevo desafío.
最好的选择，我想要的，幸运的是它最终发生了。
The best option, what I wanted and luckily it ended up happening.
La mejor opción, lo que quería y por suerte se terminó dando.
这个决定是因为我之前告诉过你的，试图找到我的......
And the decision was because what I told you before, to try to find my...
Y la decisión fue porque lo que te decía antes, de intentar encontrar mi...
我作为一名足球运动员在会谈后帮助球队的最佳版本。
my best version as a footballer to help the team after the talks I had.
mi mejor versión como futbolista para así ayudar al equipo después de las charlas que tuve.
和同事们，和 Cholo 一起，他们给了我保证……
with colleagues, with Cholo, they gave me the guarantees to...
con compañeros, con el Cholo, me daban los avales para...
因为我的感受，所以我们正在寻找。
for what I felt, so we are in that search.
para eso que yo sentía, entonces estamos en esa búsqueda.
你在那里错过了什么？
What were you missing there?
¿Qué te faltaba allá?
我不知道我是否错过了什么。
I don't know if I was missing something.
No sé si me faltaba algo.
我一直都很好。
I was always fine.
Siempre estuve bien.
我在那里的两年里，俱乐部对我很好。
The club has treated me very well the two years I was there.
El club me ha tratado muy bien los dos años que estuve.
我们赢得了一些东西，我度过了美好的时刻。
We have won things, I have had great moments.
Hemos ganado cosas, he pasado grandes momentos.
但出于个人原因，我想要一些不同的东西，改变，所以这就是决定。
but for a personal reason I wanted something different, a change, so that was the decision.
pero por un tema personal quería algo diferente, un cambio, así que fue por eso la decisión.
你认为这种方式...
Do you think that the way of...
¿Te parece que la forma de...
关于管理俱乐部、关于乔洛、关于男孩们，阿根廷国家队的版本会让你们更接近。
of running the club, of Cholo, of the boys, the version of the Argentine National Team is going to bring you closer.
de llevar el club, del Cholo, de los chicos, te va a acercar la versión de Selección Argentina.
是的，据你所说，男孩们可能...
Yes, it could be, from what you say, the boys...
Sí, puede ser, por lo que decís, los chicos...
许多阿根廷人，因为风格，因为他们的生活方式，因为......
many Argentines, because of the style, because of how they live, because of how...
muchos argentinos, por el estilo, por cómo se vive también, por cómo...
无论是在这里的比赛中，我想这就是为什么，从侧面来看，是的，有点是。
be it in the games here, I think that's why, seeing it from that side, yes, a little yes.
sea en los partidos acá, creo que por ese, viéndolo de ese lado sí, un poco sí.
乔洛的踢球方式和斯卡洛尼相似吗？
Is Cholo's way of playing similar to Scaloni's?
¿Tienen similitud la forma de jugar del Cholo con la de Scaloni?
是的，有些事情是，但就像每个技术人员一样，他有他的......
Yes, some things are, but like every technician he has his...
Sí, algunas cosas sí, pero como todo técnico tiene su...
他的想法，他看待足球的方式，以及如何处理不同时刻的方式。
His idea, his way of seeing football, of how to handle different moments.
Su idea, su forma de ver el fútbol, de cómo manejar los diferentes momentos.
选举略有不同。
The elections are a little different.
Las elecciones son un poco diferentes.
因为好吧，比赛更少了，你不是一直都在场，有比赛，锦标赛也更短。
Because well, there are fewer games, you're not there all the time, there are competitions, shorter tournaments.
Porque bueno, son menos partidos, no estás todo el tiempo, por ahí son competiciones, torneos más cortos.
诸如此类的事情，但显然有相似之处。
and things like that, but there are similarities, obviously.
y esas cosas, pero sí que hay similitudes, obviamente.
你是怎么跟佩佩说再见的？
How did you say goodbye to Pepe?
¿Cómo te despediste de Pepe?
不，好吧，事实是我不能去曼彻斯特，但是......
No, well, the truth is that I couldn't go to Manchester, but...
No, bueno, la verdad que no pude ir a Manchester, pero...
但我确实知道，在我即将签约或签约后的那些日子里，我记不太清楚了。
But I do know that in those days when I was about to sign or after I signed I don't remember well.
pero sí que en esos días cuando ya estaba por firmar o después que firmé no recuerdo bien.
我们聊了聊，我感谢他所做的一切。
We talked and I thanked him for everything.
Nos hablamos y le agradecí por todo.
因为岁月，因为信任，因为待遇，因为我学到的一切，因为我经历的一切，是整个教练组。
Because of the years, because of the trust, because of the treatment, because of everything I learned, because of everything I experienced, it was the entire coaching staff.
por los años, por la confianza, por el trato, por todo lo que aprendí, por todo lo que vivía, era todo el cuerpo técnico.
在场的所有人和他也感谢我，因为已经两年了。
All the people there and he also thanked me because it was two years.
toda la gente de ahí y él también de su parte me agradeció porque fueron dos años
太棒了，从来没有制造过任何问题，从来没有做过任何事情并提供帮助。
amazing, never made any problem, never did anything and helped.
increíble, nunca hice ningún problema, nunca nada y ayudé.
在俱乐部取得非常好的成就。
to achieve very nice things in the club.
para lograr cosas muy lindas en el club.
他问我，如果有一天我能去的话就好了，因为所有的人......
He asked me that if I had one day it would be nice to go because all the people...
Me pidió que si tuviera algún día sería lindo ir porque toda la gente...
他会很兴奋地跟我打招呼，所以当他有机会时他可能会去那里。
He was going to be very excited for me to say hello, so when he has the chance he might go there.
Le iba a hacer mucha ilusión que lo saludara, así que cuando tenga oportunidad quizás vaya para allá.
离开后你给自己写过信吗？
Have you written to yourself after leaving?
¿Te has escrito después de la salida?
看看你怎么样。
to see how you were.
para ver cómo estabas.
不，那一刻我对自己说。
No, I spoke to myself at that moment.
No, hablé solo en ese momento.
这也是事实，我也是……
It is also true that I am...
También es verdad que yo estoy...
我们在这里也有很多游戏。
We are here with many games, that too.
Estamos acá con muchos partidos, eso también.
这个赛季有点困难，但我认为会有机会。
During the season it's been a little difficult, but I think there will be an opportunity.
Durante la temporada por ahí un poco difícil, pero creo que ya habrá oportunidad.
您还想再出去一次吗？
Would you have liked another outing?
¿Te hubiera gustado otra salida?
我的意思是，因为你说过，他回应说，好吧，每个人都想参加比赛。
I mean, because there was that statement from you, that he responded, well, everyone wants to play.
Digo, porque hubo esa declaración tuya, que él respondió, bueno, todos quieren jugar.
但有18名选手，听起来很直接。
but there are 18 players, which sounded very direct.
pero son 18 jugadores, que sonó muy de frente.
您希望以不同的方式离开曼城吗？
Would you have liked to have had a different exit from City?
¿Te hubiera gustado tener una salida diferente del City?
不，我不认为这有什么不好。
No, I don't think it was in a bad way.
No, yo no creo que haya sido de una forma mala.
我总是和...
I always talked to...
Yo siempre hablé con...
我当时说的话是完全真诚的。
with complete sincerity what I said at that moment.
con total sinceridad lo que dije en ese momento.
然后我解释了它，是的，这听起来可能有点糟糕，它也有点......
Then I explained it and yes it may have sounded a bit bad, it's also a bit what...
Después lo expliqué y sí puede haber sonado un poco mal, también es un poco lo que...
社交网络和媒体放大了什么。
what is magnified by social networks, by the media.
lo que se agranda por redes sociales, por los medios.
还有什么被扔掉了。
And what is thrown away.
Y lo que se tira.
我只是说...
I simply said that...
Simplemente dije que...
这将是对发生的事情的分析并预测未来可能发生的事情，我总是说我......
that it was going to be an analysis of what happened and project what could come in the future, I always said that I had...
que iba a ser un análisis de lo que pasó y proyectar lo que podía venir en el futuro, siempre dije que tuve...
我在俱乐部度过了一段美好的时光，我非常高兴，非常舒服。
that I had had a great time at the club, that I was very happy, very comfortable.
que la había pasado muy bien en el club, que estuve muy feliz, muy a gusto.
他们只是...
They were just...
Simplemente fueron...
缺少解释的词语或者有点扭曲了事情，但一切都很好。
words that were missing to explain or that distorted things a little, but all was well.
palabras que faltaron para explicar o por ahí que se distorsionan un poco las cosas, pero todo bien.
朱利安·佩佩是教练之一。
Julián, Pepe is one of the coaches.
Julián, Pepe es uno de los entrenadores.
获得更多的名气，获得更多的成功。
with more fame, with more successes.
con más fama, con más éxitos.
它给你留下了什么？
What does it leave you?
¿Qué te deja?
这两年在曼城的时光给你留下了什么？
What has your time at City left you in those two years?
¿Qué te ha dejado ese paso por el City esos dos años?
也有可能从那个喷泉里喝水。
that possibility also of drinking from that fountain.
esa posibilidad también de beber de esa fuente.
非常非常的实话。
Very, very much, the truth.
Mucho, mucho, la verdad.
从阿根廷搬到这里也是一个很大的变化。
It was also a big change to move from Argentina.
También fue un cambio grande pasar de Argentina.
欧洲，另一个国家，另一种文化，另一种语言。
Europe, another country, another culture, another language.
Europa, otro país, otra cultura, otro idioma.
有很多事情。
There were many things.
Fueron muchas las cosas.
我适应得很好，成长了很多，学到了很多东西。
I adapted very well, I grew a lot, I learned a lot of things.
Me adapté muy bien, crecí mucho, aprendí muchas cosas.
好吧，如果你能说出我的名字，有很多，但是……如果你必须选择一个……
Well, if you could name me, there are many but... If you had to choose one...
Bueno, si me pudiera mencionar, son muchas pero... Si tuvieras que quedarte con una...
从教练组、工作人员、组织方式以及一切方面。
from the coaching staff, the staff, the way the organization is and everything.
del cuerpo técnico, del staff, la forma en que está la organización y todo.
同事也是，但我想我会留下来......
colleagues too, but I think I'll stay...
compañeros también, pero creo que me quedo...
他们如何处理一切，不仅是教练组、球员，还有整个俱乐部。
With how they deal with everything, not only the coaching staff, the players, but the entire club.
Con cómo enfrentan todo, no solo el cuerpo técnico, los jugadores, sino todo el club.
每场比赛，俱乐部的每个人都贡献自己的一粒沙，让一切顺利进行。
Every game, every person in the club contributes their grain of sand to make everything work.
Cada partido, cada persona del club aporta su granito de arena para que todo funcione.
好吧，或者尝试让它更接近完美，所以我会坚持下去。
well or try to make it closer to perfection, so I'll stick with that.
bien o trate de hacerlo más cerca a la perfección, así que me quedo con eso.
瞧，我在这里已经20年了。
Look, I've been here for 20 years.
Mirá, llevo 20 años acá.
莱蒂的签约从来没有引起如此多的期望，如此之多......
Never has a Lety signing raised so many expectations, so much...
Nunca un fichaje de la Lety levantó tantas expectativas, tanta...
情感前
emotion ago
emoción hace
你彻底改变了俱乐部。
You have revolutionized the club.
Has revolucionado el club.
你感受到人们、孩子们的这种爱吗？
Do you feel this affection from the people, from the children?
¿Sentís este cariño de la gente, de los niños?
新团体的现实发生了怎样的变化？
How has the reality of the new group transformed a little?
¿Cómo ha transformado un poco la realidad del rupto llegado?
是的，对不起，我从第一刻起就感觉到了，甚至在签字之前。
Yes, I'm sorry, I felt it from the first moment, even before signing.
Sí, lo siento, lo sentí desde el primer momento, incluso antes de firmar.
它告诉你什么？
What does it tell you?
¿Qué te dice?
人们在社交网络上发布了很多东西。
People, on social networks, posted many things.
La gente, en las redes sociales, ponía muchas cosas.
嗯，当我到达时也到处都是。
Well, when I arrived there was also everywhere.
Bueno, cuando llegué también por todos lados.
当我遇到人时，他们对我说非常好话。
When I meet people they say very nice things to me.
Cuando me cruzo gente me dice cosas muy lindas.
所以，从那部分来看，也没有什么，不仅......
So nothing, from that part too, not only...
Así que nada, de esa parte también, no solo...
所有人、整个俱乐部的热情，即使不是我的热情。
The enthusiasm of all the people, of the entire club, if not mine too.
La ilusión de toda la gente, de todo el club, si no mía también.
我来到这里，带着很多...
I come here with a lot...
Vengo acá con mucha...
正如我之前所说，我怀着很高的期望，试图找到我最好的版本。
With high expectations, as I said before, I tried to find my best version.
Con lindas expectativas, como decía antes, intenté encontrar mi mejor versión.
帮助球队，与俱乐部一起取得美好的成就。
to help the team, to achieve nice things with the club.
para ayudar al equipo, para conseguir cosas lindas con el club.
我们正处于这个时代。
We are in this time.
Estamos en este tiempo.
尝试从少到多去寻找我们都想要的东西。
Trying to go from less to more to go in search of that which is what we all want.
Intentando ir de menos a más para ir en búsqueda de eso que es lo que todos queremos.
朱利安即将来到德比，可能是值得观看的酒吧
Julián is coming to the derby, probably the bar to watch
Julián se viene al derbi, probablemente el listón para ver
阿莱蒂怎么样？
How is the aleti?
¿Cómo está el aleti?
我这里有一张照片。
And here I have a photo.
Y aquí tengo una foto.
因为你会再次遇见一个人。
Because you are going to meet someone again.
Porque te vas a volver a encontrar con alguien.
随着.
With the.
Con él.
¡呃？
¿Eh?
是谁？
Who is it?
¿Quién es?
有没有一种...？
Is there a kind of...?
¿Hay una especie de...?
世界杯迷你决赛。
World Cup minifinal.
de minifinal de Copa del Mundo.
我是说，有罗德里、你、安杰利托……
I mean, there's Rodri, you, Angelito...
Digo, está Rodri, vos, Angelito...
是的，莫利纳。
Yes, Molina.
Sí, Molina.
另一边是vapecho、amení、mendí...
On the other side are vapecho, amení, mendí...
Del otro lado están vapecho, amení, mendí...
格里西站在你这边，这是真的。
And Grisí is on your side, it's true.
Y Grisí está de tu lado, es verdad.
他会跟你开玩笑吗？
Does he play a joke on you?
¿Te hace alguna broma?
他有告诉你任何关于决赛的事情吗？
Did he tell you anything about the final?
¿Te dijo algo de la final?
不，不是决赛。
No, not from the final.
No, de la final no.
但每边有四个。
but there are four on each side.
pero hay cuatro de cada lado.
你想过这个吗？
Did you think about this?
¿Lo pensaste esto?
不，事实是我没有这样想过。
No, the truth is that I had not thought about it this way.
No, la verdad que no lo había pensado de esta forma.
但是，是的，显然德比非常重要，也许也是......
But yes, obviously the derby is very important, perhaps also one of the...
Pero sí, obviamente que el derby es muy importante, quizás también uno de los...
世界上最重要的事情并且有可能
of the most important thing in the world and have the possibility of
de lo más importante del mundo y tener la posibilidad de
来到这里，玩起来真是太好了。
Being here, playing it is very nice.
De estar acá, de jugarlo es muy lindo.
我并不像你说的那样，但这对每个人来说都将是一场非常重要的比赛。
I didn't see it that way as you say, but it is going to be a very important game for everyone.
No lo veía así como lo decís vos, pero sí que va a ser un partido muy importante para todos.
但这并不能阻止我们成为联赛中的另一场比赛。
but it doesn't stop us from being just another game in the League.
pero tampoco nos deja de ser un partido más dentro de la Liga.
考虑塞尔塔，我们必须不断增加，不断增加......
to think about Celta, we have to keep adding, keep adding to...
a pensar en el Celta, tenemos que seguir sumando, seguir sumando para...
但是嘿，他们正在战斗。
but hey, they are in the fight.
pero bueno están en la pelea.
他们是最令人兴奋的两笔签约，一名来自马德里，另一名来自马竞。
They are the two most exciting signings, one from Madrid and the other from Atleti.
Son los dos fichajes más ilusionantes, uno del Madrid y otro del Atleti.
他们觉得...
They feel that...
Sienten ese...
与基利安·姆巴佩的对决。
that duel with Kylian Mbappé.
ese duelo con Kylian Mbappé.
这两个人在某种程度上在首都的两家具乐部中引起了最大的兴奋。
to be the two men who in some way have generated the greatest excitement in the two clubs in the capital.
ser los dos hombres que de alguna manera han generado la mayor ilusión en los dos clubes de la capital.
好吧，我不知道这是否是个人悲伤之类的，但是......
Well, I don't know if it's personal grief and that way, but...
Bueno, no sé si duelo personal y de esa forma, pero...
但正如你所说，这是事实，它唤醒了许多人的热情，唤醒了社交网络上谈论的一切的热情......
but it is true, as you say, it awakens the enthusiasm of many people, of everything that is talked about on social networks and that type...
pero sí que verdad, como decís, despierta la ilusión de mucha gente, de todo lo que se habla en las redes sociales y ese tipo...
那种事我在里面看到了
that kind of thing and I see it in
ese tipo de cosas y yo lo veo en
一如既往地继续工作，尽力而为，确保一切顺利。
continue working in the same way as always, do your best, make sure things go well.
seguir trabajando de la misma forma de siempre, dar lo mejor, que las cosas salgan bien.
在球场上，帮助球队，从而一点一点地继续补充。
on the court, help the team and thus continue adding step by step little by little.
en la cancha, ayudar al equipo y así seguir sumando paso a paso de a poco.
我不会尝试去思考更多的事情，或者过多地思考这类事情。
I don't try to think beyond that or give much thought to that kind of thing.
No trato de pensar más allá ni darle mucha vuelta a ese tipo de cosas.
我说，从心理角度来看，你以不同的方式打高尔夫球，因为……
You work on golf in a different way, I say, from a mental perspective, since the topic of...
Trabajas el golf de una manera diferente, digo, desde lo mental, que ahora está muy de moda el tema de la...
脑力工作，有教练和专注。
of mental work, with a coach and focusing.
del trabajo mental, con coach y enfocarte.
对于一名以进球为生并充满期待的前锋来说。
for a striker who lives from the goal and with the expectation that has been generated for him.
para un delantero que vive del gol y con la expectativa que se le ha generado.
这让我很好奇。
It makes me curious.
Me causa curiosidad.
你有什么特殊的工作可以让你不用担心得分吗？
Do you have any special job so you don't have that anxiety about scoring?
¿Tenés algún trabajo especial para no tener esa ansiedad de cara a marcar?
不，有具体的东西。
No, something specific.
No, algo puntual.
我很平静。
I'm pretty calm.
Soy bastante tranquilo.
我觉得工作没钱...
I think work doesn't pay...
Creo que el trabajo si no paga...
第二天左右随着时间的推移以某种方式说话。
the next day or so to speak in some way over time.
al otro día o por decirlo así de alguna manera con el tiempo.
取得成果，我不会发疯，所以作为前锋就想进球。
bear fruit, I don't go crazy, so as a striker you want to score.
dar a sus frutos, no me vuelvo loco, así que uno como delantero quiere marcar.
是的，有很多人和事的热情，但什么也没有，我想……
Yes, there is the enthusiasm of many people and everything, but nothing, I think...
Sí está la ilusión de mucha gente y todo, pero nada, creo que...
最重要的是从其他方面也能帮助球队。
that the most important thing is to help the team from other aspects as well.
que lo más importante es ayudar al equipo desde otros aspectos también.
显然，作为一名前锋，你想要进球，因为这也是......
Obviously as a striker you want to score goals because that is also the way to...
Obviamente como delantero uno quiere hacer goles porque es la forma también de...
提供帮助，这有助于赢得一切，但是哦，好吧。
to help and it serves to win and everything, but oh well.
de ayudar y sirve para ganar y todo, pero bueno.
我不会发疯，我知道他们会来，那里也有条纹。
I'm not going crazy, I know they're going to come, there are streaks out there too.
No me vuelvo loco, sé que van a llegar, que por ahí son rachas también.
所以你越疯狂，情况就越糟糕。
So the crazier you get, the worse it is.
Así que mientras más loco te vuelves, peor es.
所以你必须保持冷静。
So you have to be calm.
Así que hay que estar tranquilos.
又一个物体。
One more object.
Un objeto más.
这个有重。
This one weighs.
Este pesa.
看看你是否用这种方式打开它。
Let's see if you open it this way.
A ver si lo abrís de esta manera.
但你养大了，对吧？
But you raised the big one, right?
Pero vos levantaste la grandota, no?
你看，你知道马竞打了三场决赛，但他们还没有赢过。
Look, you know that Atleti played three finals, and that they still haven't won.
Mira, vos sabés que la Atleti jugó tres finales, que todavía no la ha ganado.
赢得决赛需要什么？
What does it take to win a final?
¿Qué hace falta para ganar una final?
你玩过并且赢过吗？
Have you played and won?
¿Ha jugado y ha ganado?
在一场比赛的决赛中，这取决于很多因素。
In the final of a match it depends on many things.
En la final de un partido depende de muchas cosas.
在那里，一个细节标志着...
There, a detail marks the...
Por ahí un detalle marca la...
区别在于，重要的是要一步一步地到达那里，正如我刚才所说的。
the difference, the important thing is to get there, step by step, as I just said.
la diferencia, lo importante es llegar hasta ahí, paso a paso, como decía recién.
这场比赛现在才刚刚开始。
This competition is just starting now.
Recién arranca ahora esta competición.
你必须像这样从一场比赛到另一场比赛，一年中有很多比赛。
You have to go from game to game like that, there are many games during the year.
Hay que ir así de partido a partido, hay muchos partidos durante el año.
竞争很多，所以你必须在时机成熟时做好准备。
a lot of competition, so you have to prepare to be ready when it's time.
mucha competencia, así que hay que prepararse para estar listo cuando toque.
当你看到它时，你的脸发光了。
Your face lit up when you saw it.
Se te ilumino la cara cuando la viste.
显然，这非常好，可以说是世界上最好的赛事之一，也是俱乐部最好的赛事之一。
Obviously it is very nice, one of the best tournaments in the world, so to speak, also the club.
Obviamente es muy linda, uno de los mejores torneos del mundo, como decir, también el club.
他没有得到机会，他非常接近实现这一目标，人们对此感到非常兴奋。
He has not been given the opportunity, he was very close to achieving it, people are very excited about it.
no se le ha dado la oportunidad, estuvo muy cerca de conseguirlo, a la gente le hace mucha ilusión.
进入欧冠决赛。
to reach the Champions League final.
para llegar a la final de la Champions.
作为一个团队？
As a team?
¿Como equipo?
是的，马竞。
Yes, Atleti.
Sí, el Atleti.
你有一支球队能进入决赛吗？
Do you have a team to reach the final?
¿Tiene equipo para llegar a la final?
是的，我们显然相信并感觉我们可以。
Yes, we obviously believe and feel that we can.
Sí, obviamente creemos y sentimos que podemos.
凭借我们的阵容，任何人都可以对抗它，所以是的，它可能会发生，但正如我刚才在这里告诉你的。
With the squad we have, anyone can fight it, so yes it can happen, but as I just told you here.
Con el plantel que tenemos podemos pelearla cualquiera, así que sí que se puede dar, pero como te decía recién aquí.
渐渐地，今年我们也有很多新加入的球员，所以我们要去。
Little by little we are also many new players who joined this year, so we are going.
De a poco también somos muchos jugadores que nos incorporamos nuevos este año, así que vamos a ir.
从少到多。
From less to more.
De menos a más.
对阵曼城的决赛会是什么样？
What would a final against City be like?
¿Cómo sería una final contra el City?
我们来投影一下。
Let's project.
Proyectemos.
为你。
For you.
Para vos.
这是一场艰难的比赛，就像所有比赛一样，就像对阵任何人一样，在这场比赛中更是如此。
It is a difficult match like everything, like against anyone, and even more so in this competition.
Es un partido difícil como todo, como contra cualquiera, y más en esta competición.
然后，正如我之前所说，有了我们的武器，我们就可以与任何人作战。
Then with our weapons we can, as I said before, fight anyone.
Después con nuestras armas podemos, como dije antes, pelearle a cualquiera.
戴尔，好。
Dale, good.
Dale, bien.
我们从物体出发。
We move from object.
Pasamos de objeto.
我只携带它一小会儿。
I carry it for just a little while.
La llevo por un ratito nada más.
这个很漂亮。
This one is beautiful.
Esta está linda.
好吧，我们来做个练习吧。
Okay look, let's do an exercise.
Vale mira, vamos a hacer un ejercicio.
西布隆，在对阵阿拉伯的比赛后写信给朱利安·阿尔瓦雷斯。
Cibron, write to Julián Álvarez after the game against Arabia.
Cibrón, escribíle a Julián Álvarez después del partido contra Arabia.
你有什么建议吗？
What do you recommend?
¿Qué le recomiendas?
你有什么建议？
What do you suggest?
¿Qué le sugerís?
你对他说什么？
What do you say to him?
¿Qué le decís?
我必须写。
I have to write.
Tengo que escribir.
戴尔.
Dale.
宝贵的。
Precious.
Precioso.
你会读给我听吗？
Will you read it to me?
¿Me lo lees?
宁静，工作，相信，美好的事情即将到来。
Tranquility, work, believe, beautiful things are coming.
Tranquilidad, trabajo, creer, se vienen cosas lindas.
但？
But?
Sí, ¿no?
非常好。
Very good.
Muy buena.
请你帮我签名好吗？
And will you sign it for me, please?
¿Y me la firmás, porfa?
好吧，先生、教练、选择者，莱昂内尔·斯卡洛尼。
Well, the mister, the coach, the selector, Lionel Scaloni.
Bueno, el mister, el entrenador, el seleccionador, Lionel Scaloni.
与玩家交谈非常重要。
It is very important to talk to the player.
Es muy de hablar con el jugador.
有一场演讲给你留下了深刻的印象，明白吗？
There is a talk that has marked you, see?
Hay una charla que te ha marcado, ¿ven?
呃...
Eh...
我记得有一场比赛，但我不记得那是哪场比赛之后的事了，在赢得世界杯之后。
I remember one that I don't remember after what game it was, after having won the World Cup as well.
Recuerdo una que no me acuerdo después de qué partido fue, después de haber ganado el Mundial también.
他与我和劳塔罗交谈，并对在场的两人非常真诚
who spoke to me and Lautaro and was very sincere with the two who are there
que nos habló a mí y a Lautaro y fue muy sincero con los dos que por ahí está
谁必须玩，谁不玩。
Who has to play, who doesn't.
quién tiene que jugar, quién no.
他的观点对我们来说非常诚实。
His point of view was very honest with us.
Su punto de vista fue muy sincero con nosotros.
他没有说谁会上场，谁不会上场，但具体取决于比赛，他的感受如何。
He didn't say who was going to play and who wasn't, but depending on the game, what he feels.
No dijo quién iba a jugar y quién no, pero dependiendo del partido, de lo que sienta.
这是非常可贵的，因为它非常真诚，这是不多见的。
That is very valuable because it is very sincere, which is not seen many times.
Eso es muy valorable porque es muy sincero, que no se ve muchas veces.
他向你解释事情。
He explains things to you.
Te explica las cosas.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
朱利安...
Julian...
Julián...
由于里奥受伤，他们有机会在没有里奥的情况下比赛。
They had the chance, because Leo was injured, to play without Leo.
Tuvieron la posibilidad, porque Leo estaba lesionado, de jugar sin Leo.
没有里奥在国家队打球有多难？
How difficult is it to play without Leo in the national team?
¿Cuán difícil es jugar sin Leo en la selección?
莱奥在国家队已经很多年了，有点奇怪。
It has been many years that Leo has been in the national team and it is a bit strange.
Han sido muchos años de que Leo está en la selección y resulta un poco raro.
因为球队的比赛方式有点明显，因为你知道在哪里
because well the way the team plays is a little marked because you know where
porque bueno la forma de jugar de la selección un poco se marca porque vos sabes dónde
他移动的地方，由他在场上占据的位置决定。
where he moves, by the place in the field that he occupies.
por donde se mueve él, por el sitio en el campo que él ocupa.
现在有些比赛他还没有参加，我们尝试去参加
Now there have been some games that he hasn't been to and we try to
Ahora han sido algunos partidos que no ha estado y tratamos de
适应，那种不那么明显的变化。
of adapting, of that change that is not so noticeable.
de adaptarnos, de ese cambio que no se nota tanto.
你要把它封印在Monte de la Leo吗？
Are you sealing it to the Monte de la Leo?
¿Lo vais sellando al Monte de la Leo?
是的，我认为这取决于他。
Yes, I think it depends on him.
Sí, yo creo que depende de él.
他的身体看起来很好，只要他愿意，他就感觉……
He looks good physically and as long as he feels like it, he feels that...
Él se lo ve bien físicamente y mientras él tenga ganas sienta que...
谁可以提供帮助并愿意在那里。
who can help and wants to be there.
que puede ayudar y quiere estar.